http://www.skydiveperris.com/privacy-policy

HomePrivacy Policy
Privacy Policy
Our commitment to your privacy
Your privacy is important to us.  To better protect your privacy the following notice explains the information we collect, how it is used, how it is safeguarded, and how to contact us if you have any concerns.
What information is collected
In order to process your order we collect personal information including your full name, billing and shipping address, email address, phone number, and credit/debit card or other payment information.  In order to participate you will be asked to provide identification such as a document number on a state-issued identification.  We also may collect information related to how you found our web site including which advertisements or links were used and the computer systems and servers used to access the site.
How that information is used
Your personal information will be used to process your order and to deliver products, services, and promotional information to you and to verify your identity with respect to your purchase and acceptance of the Statement of Risk.
When you order online we will email you with your order status and notifications in the event that there is any problem with fulfilling your order.  We do not sell or rent your personal information to others unless you so authorize.  You may opt-out of promotional mailings at any time.
Our commitment to the security of your data
We are committed to the privacy of the information you provide to us.  It will in no way be sold or otherwise furnished to any other party or parties.  Information collected along with serial numbers of items purchased may be retained in our database for verification purposes only.  We secure your information during transmission by using Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) encryption.
Family Owned Since 1976
